So I'd like you to apply what you just learned about arraylist
أود منك تطبيق ما تعلمته للتو عن القائمة الصفيفة
to modify the numbers activity.
لتعديل نشاط الأرقام،
To represent the list of vocabulary words as an arraylist of strings,
لتمثيل قائمة مفردات الكلمات كقائمة صفيفة من السلاسل،
rather than an array of strings.
بدلًا من مصفوفة السلاسل.
Now, if you are creating this app in a professional environment,
والآن، إذا كنت تُنشئ هذا التطبيق في بيئة محترفة،
either arraylist or an array would be valid.
ستكون إما القائمة الصفيفة أو المصفوفة صالحة.
On the other hand, if our app connected to the Internet and
من ناحية، إذا اتصل تطبيقك بالإنترنت
will continue to grow with new words over time.
ستواصل الزيادة بكلمات جديدة بمرور الوقت.
Then a list would probably be more appropriate, so
لذلك ربما تكون القائمة ملائمة أكثر،
even though our app won't get new words from the internet.
رغم أن تطبيقنا لن يحصل على كلمات جديدة من الإنترنت.
Within the context of this course, I'd still prefer to use an array list.
داخل سياق هذه الدورة، لا زلت أفضل استخدام القائمة الصفيفة،
Because it's easier to add additional words without worrying about needing to
لأنه يكون من الأسهل إضافة كلمات جديدة بدون القلق بشأن الحاجة إلى
change the size of the array.
تغيير حجم المصفوفة.
So, for the first part of this exercise, I'd like you to modify the app, so
لذلك، بالنسبة لأول جزء في هذا التدريب، أود منك تعديل التطبيق، لذا
we store the words in an array list, instead of an array.
نحن نُخزّن الكلمات في قائمة صفيفة، بدلًا من مصفوفة.
Now, the words should stay the same.
والآن، ينبغي أن تبقى الكمات كما هي.
It should be the numbers one through ten spelled out, and
ينبغي أن تكون الأرقام محددة من واحد إلى عشرة،
be sure to update the log messages.
وتأكد من تحديث رسائل السجل.
So we print out each element of the array list, instead of from the array.
إذن نكتب كل عنصر في القائمة الصفيفة، بدلًا من المصفوفة.
And remember, you can always reference this table that summarizes how the code
وتذكّر أن بإمكانك دائمًا الرجوع إلى هذا الجدول الذي يُلخّص كيف يختلف الكود
is different between an array an array list.
بين المصوفة والقائمة الصفيفة.
And when you run the latest version of the code on your device,
وعندما تُشغّل أحدث إصدار من الكود على جهازك،
there shouldn't be any changes in the appearance of the app.
لا ينبغي أن تكون هناك أي تغييرات في مظهر التطبيق.
And rememberm you can check the logs to verify that the list was
وتذكّر أن بإمكانك فحص السجلات للتحقق من إنشاء تلك القائمة
created properly.
بشكل ملائم.
And go ahead and check these boxes when you're done.
وامضِ قدمًا وتحقق من تلك الصناديق بعد أن تنتهي.